Reading
Who am I?
Over time I have been changed quite a lot.
I began as a calculating machine in France in 1642.
Although I was young I could simplify difficult sums.
After I was programmed by an operator who used cards with holes,
I could "think" logically and produce an answer quicker than any person.
At that time it was considered a technological revolution and the start of my "artificial intelligence".
In 1936 my real father, Alan Turing,
a universal machine to solve any difficult mathematical problem.
However, this reality also worried my designers.
As time went by, I was made smaller.
These changes only became possible as my memory improved.
First it was stored in tubes, then on transistors and later on very small chips.
As a result I totally changed my shape.
As I have grown older I have also grown smaller.
Over time my memory has developed so much that,
like an elephant, I never forget anything I have been told!
And my memory became so large that even I couldn’t believe it!
I was able to share my knowledge with others through the World Wide Web.
I have become very important in communication,
finance and trade.
I have also been put into robots and used to make mobile phones as well as help
with medical operations.
I have even been put into space rockets and sent to explore the Moon
and Mars.
Anyhow, my goal is to provide humans with a life of high quality.
I am now truly filled with happiness that I am a devoted friend
and helper of the human race!